JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 2
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA! MEETS ANGELO
AQUA NECKLACE
ANJURO KATAGIRI
— 3 DAYS LATER —
MORIOH LANDMARK 1
ANGELO'S ROCK
ONE MINUTE WALK FROM
MORIOH JOZENJI STREET BUS STOP #3
EPISODE 3
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 1